So, we discussed about the incident response scenario for exfiltration things.
So, we know they are using R-tone and media for exfiltration, right.
So, from our expect we can do some things like we can block the hash of R-tone.exe.
In EDR or the platform, the security platform whatever we are using.
First of all, as we know the mega was involved in exfiltration to upload data in the cloud,
we can block the hash for we can block the IP of mega cloud.
In the firewall or EDR or any different mechanism tool, that will help us to prevent
more data get exfiltration into the cloud environment.
So, we have discussed plenty of incident response scenario in collection, in lateral movement,
a lot of tactics, but if you see in exfiltration related activity, we need to know who is
the user.
So, in our scenario, this is the user who performs.
So, we can reset, we can temporarily disable this user and reset the credentials, as
well as blocking the IP, isolating the machine and blocking the hash of R-tone.exe.
That will help you to get prevent from more data get expelled from the machine or from
the organization.
So, my scenario is, if you block the R-tone.exe, the threat tactics will not able to
use R-tone anymore inside the organization.
So, if you block the mega cloud IP, so the threat tactics will not able to access mega
to upload their sensitive files.
So, the exfiltration tactics will be get stopped, once we get resetting the credentials
or disabling the user account, so we can stop the threat tactics to further executing commands
from the machine.
So, once we isolate the machine, we can completely cut out the connection from the threat
tactics to move further, to move more further, more exfiltration device.
So, I hope you have enjoyed this section, we will continue our discussion in the next
to section. See you guys, bye bye.